<stratagems>

    <square value="1">
        <title>Command Reroll</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            In any phase, just after you have made a HIT ROLL, WOUND ROLL, DAMAGE ROLL, SAVING THROW, ADVANCE
            ROLL, CHARGE ROLL, DESPERATE ESCAPE TEST, HAZARDOUS TEST, or NUMBER OF ATTACKS ROLL

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            You re-roll that ROLL, TEST, or SAVE.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Counter-Offensive -->
    <square value="2">
        <title>Counter-Offensive</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            2CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            FIGHT PHASE, just after an ENEMY UNIT has fought

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One UNIT from your army that is within Engagement Range of one or more enemy units and that has not already
            been selected to fight this phase.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Your unit fights next.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Epic Challenge -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Epic Challenge</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            FIGHT PHASE, when a CHARACTER unit from your army that is within Engagement Range of one or more attached
            units is selected to fight.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One CHARACTER model in your unit.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Until the end of the phase, all melee attacks made by that model have the PRECISION ability.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Insane Bravery -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Insane Bravery</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            BATTLE-SHOCK step of your COMMAND PHASE, just after you have failed a BATTLE-SHOCK TEST taken for a unit
            from your army.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            The unit from your army that the BATTLE-SHOCK test was just taken for.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Your unit is treated as having passed that test instead, and is not BATTLE-SHOCKED as a result.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Grenade -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Grenade</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your SHOOTING PHASE.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One GRENADES unit from your army that is not within engagement range of any enemy units and has not been
            selected to shoot this phase.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Select one enemy unit that is not within Engagement range of any units from your army and is within 8 inches
            of and visible to your GRENADES unit. Roll six D6: for each 4+, that enemy unit suffers 1 MW.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Tank Shock -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Tank Shock</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your CHARGE PHASE.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One VEHICLE unit from your army

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Until the end of the phase, after your unit ends a Charge move, select one enemy unit within Engagement
            Range of it, then select one melee weapon your unit is equipped with. Roll a number of D6 equal to that
            weapon’s Strength characteristic. If that Strength characteristic is greater than that enemy unit’s
            Toughness characteristic, roll two additional D6. For each 5+, that enemy unit suffers 1 mortal wound (to a
            maximum of 6 mortal wounds).
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Rapid Ingress -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Rapid Ingress</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            End of your opponent’s MOVEMENT phase

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One unit from your army that is in RESERVES.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            You cannot use this Stratagem to enable a unit to arrive on the battlefield during a battle round it would
            not normally be able to do so in

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Your unit can arrive on the battlefield as if it were the Reinforcements step of your Movement phase.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Fire Overwatch -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Fire Overwatch</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your opponent’s MOVEMENT or CHARGE phase, just after an enemy unit is set up or when an enemy unit starts or
            ends a Normal, Advance, Fall Back or Charge move.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One unit from your army that is within 24" of that enemy unit and that would be eligible to shoot if it were
            your SHOOTING phase.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            Until the end of the phase, each time a model in your unit makes a ranged attack, an unmodified Hit roll of
            6 is required to score a hit, irrespective of the attacking weapon’s Ballistic Skill or any modifiers. You
            can only use this Stratagem once per turn.

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Your unit can shoot that enemy unit as if it were your Shooting phase.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Go to ground -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Go to ground</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your opponent’s SHOOTING phase, just after an enemy unit has selected its targets.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One INFANTRY unit from your army that was selected as the target of one or more of the attacking unit’s
            attacks.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Until the end of the phase, all models in your unit have a 6+ invulnerable save and have the Benefit of
            Cover.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Smokescreen -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Smokescreen</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your opponent’s SHOOTING phase, just after an enemy unit has selected its targets.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One Smoke unit from your army that was selected as the target of one or more of the attacking unit’s
            attacks.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            none

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Until the end of the phase, all models in your unit have the Benefit of Cover and the Stealth ability.
        </content>
    </square>

    <!-- Heroic Intervention -->
    <square value="1">
        <title>Heroic Intervention</title>
        <content>
            <span class="red-text">COST:</span>
            1CP

            <span class="red-text">FACTION:</span>
            Core

            <span class="red-text">DETACHMENT:</span>
            null

            <span class="red-text">WHEN:</span>
            Your opponent’s CHARGE phase, just after an enemy unit ends a Charge move.

            <span class="red-text">TARGET:</span>
            One unit from your army that is within 6" of that enemy unit and would be eligible to declare a charge
            against that enemy unit if it were your Charge phase.

            <span class="red-text">RESTRICTION:</span>
            You can only select a VEHICLE unit from your army if it is a Walker. Note that even if this charge is
            successful, your unit does not receive any Charge bonus this turn.

            <span class="red-text">EFFECT:</span>
            Your unit now declares a charge that targets only that enemy unit, and you resolve that charge as if it were
            your Charge phase.
        </content>
    </square>

</stratagems>